So I think that's really what it boils down to when we talk about forgive and forget.
At a certain point, you simply just have to acknowledge that you now have awareness.
You now know that this is what it is.
And it shouldn't be any deeper than that at a certain point or else it's on you.
And you have to notice when it's on you.
You have to notice when you're continuing to carry the burden and ask yourself, why am I carrying that burden?
Is it because you really that low key still want to be connected to this person?
Is it that?
Is it that that person, even though they were shady and terrible, et cetera, you still feel a connection to them in the hurt?
And that's really what's going on.
And then you got to ask yourself, why do I still want to be connected to this person?
And if it was a narcissist, baby, because they the worst and they somehow get under your skin and into your artery system.
And you got to flush it like one of them teas that they be drinking.
Mm hmm.